《比利小子》前情提要
Previously on Billy the Kid.
你为什么对我女儿
Why are you interested
感兴趣 邦尼先生
in my daughter, Mr. Bonney?
我爱她 我想娶她
I love her. I wanna marry her.
我的祖先绝不会同意
My ancestors would never approve of this.
我认为这应该让你女儿选择
I think your daughter deserves that choice.
卡特伦对浩世集团的
Mr. Catron is deeply concerned
财政状况深表关切
about the current financial position of the House.
我们知道浩世在赔钱
We know that the House is losing money
我们知道英国人汤斯顿
and we know the Englishman Tunstall's
要来瓜分我们的市场
coming to some of our markets.
我知道汤斯顿在迪克·布鲁尔的农场
I know Tunstall keeps some of his stock
养了一批牲畜 牛和马
down at Dick Brewer's ranch. His cattle and his horses.
我提议来场突袭
I say we raid'em.
嘿 给我滚出去 该死的小偷
Hey! Get off my property, you damn thieves.
我认出了杰西·埃文斯
I recognized Jesse Evans.
-驾  -我怀疑
- Hiya! - And I suspect
其他人都是七河帮的成员
the rest were a part of his 7 Rivers Gang.
作为副警长 我有权要求你
And as Deputy Sheriff, I have the authority
成立一支武装队
to insist that you organize a posse
追回所盗赃物
and go and recover the stolen goods.
走吧 快点
Let's go, come on!
出来吧 杰西
Come out, Jesse.
-把手举起来  -别开枪
Keep your hands up. - Don't shoot.
送到天花病房
Smallpox ward.
汤斯顿先生
Mr. Tunstall.
我们会以公平的价格
We'll give you a fair price for your stock,
交换你的畜群和不动产
your herds and your real estate.
作为回报呢
And in return?
你遣散你的员工
You get rid of your employees,
离开林肯县
and you leave Lincoln County.
要是我拒绝你的提议呢
And what if I refuse your offer?
那你会完蛋的
You'll be killed.
我有个计划
I have a plan.
帮杰西和他的人越狱是其中一步
It involves helping Jesse and his gang escape from jail.
什么 我们为什么要这么做
What? Why would we do that?
我给了你机会重写人生比利
I have given you a second chance in life, Billy.
我希望你用忠诚回报我
In return, I expect your loyalty.
埃文斯先生约翰·汤斯顿
Mr. Evans. John Tunstall.
就当这是求和礼物吧
Think of it as a, uh, a peace offering.
不许动
Don't move.
干得好 比利小子
Nice work, Billy boy.
谢谢
Thank you. -
我强迫你接受我的昏庸之举
By forcing you to go along with my stupid plan,
差点害死你
I nearly got you killed.
嘿 把手放在桌子上 新朋友
Hey. Hands on the table please, new friends.
你深知有危险
You were prepared to stand up for me
依然愿意为我奋不顾身
even though you knew the danger.
你到底在干什么 杰西
What the hell are you doin', Jesse?
汤斯顿真傻 这里永无和平的可能
Tunstall's a fool. There ain't no chance at peace here.
如果你想要我做搭档
If you want me to be a partner in this,
如果你想取得胜利 就得相信我
if you want to be victorious, you need to trust me.
我们还有场仗要赢
We have a war to win.
从明天开始
It starts tomorrow.
谢谢你
Thank you.
山姆 去把麦克斯文先生叫来
Sam, go fetch Mr. McSween.
是的 布鲁尔先生
Yes, sir, Mr. Brewer.
警长 有什么事吗
Sheriff, how can I help you?
-我是来给你送东西的  -这是什么
- I have something for you. - What's this?
针对这家店的法律令状
It's a legal writ against this store.
你们得即刻停业
You're gonna have to close up.
这家商店不许再做生意
This store is no longer trading.
你们都得回家了
You're all gonna have to go home.
好了 都解散吧
Please go home.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
这家店长期非法经营
This store has been trading illegally.
这得由法院说了算
That's for the courts to decide.
你非常清楚 我们会抗辩的
And you known damn well we'll fight you.
布鲁尔先生 你们没机会赢
Mr. Brewer, you have no chance.
后续还会有针对汤斯顿先生
And you can expect warrants
和麦克斯文先生的搜查令
from Mr. Tunstall and Mr. McSween.
我是副警长
I'm a Deputy.
你不能就这样越过我
You can't just go over my head.
布鲁尔先生 你的副警长任命
Mr. Brewer, your appointment as Deputy Sheriff
已被圣达菲的地方检察官托马斯·卡特伦
has been rescinded, by order of District Attorney,
下令撤销
Thomas Catron in Santa Fe.
我只能要求你交出警徽了
And I'm obliged to ask you to surrender your badge.
这究竟怎么回事
What in hell's name is happening here?
您这是在干什么 警长
What are you trying to do, Sheriff?
我只是送达令状 麦克斯文先生
I'm only serving a Iegal writ, Mr. McSween.
这是我职责所在
I'm only trying to do my duty and nothing more.
他们付了你多少钱
How much did they pay you?
我得告诉你 麦克斯文先生
I got to tell you, Mr. McSween,
你也因严重犯罪被调查
that you too are being investigated for serious crimes.
所以我建议您注意言行举止
So I suggest that you mind your manners,
小心祸从口出
keep your mouth shut.
等等 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
我听说布雷迪警长会带着武装队
So, I've heard that Sheriff Brady and a posse
于今早到达
will arrive here in the morning,
为你下达令状 没收你的一切马匹
to serve you with a writ and seize all of your horses.
他们完全不在乎这么做的合法性
They don't give a hang about the legalities.
明白了
I see.
迪克 你觉得我们该怎么办
Dick, what do you think we should do?
听你的 老板
That's up to you, boss.
比利呢
Billy?
我们应该保卫这个牧场
We should defend the ranch.
保卫你的财产
Protect your property.
我们得跟他们硬刚
We gotta fight'em.
比利说得对
Billy's right.
我们必须表明立场
We have to take a stand.
你俩谁先行去趟林肯 告诉胡安
One of you should ride into Lincoln and tell Juan Patron.
汤姆 去找查理和乔治
Tom, go get Charlie and George.
把所有武器都拿来 快
We need every gun we can get. Now.
麦克斯文先生 你需要枪吗
Mr. McSween, would you like a gun?
不需要
No.
我做了这么多年牧师
I was a pastor all these years
我发过誓 再也不碰枪
and I've sworn off ever using a gun myself.
那你就先回家吧 亚历山大
Then you best go home, Alexander.
-我们能应付得了  -我知道你们会的
- We'll manage. - I know you will.
上帝保佑你
God bless you.
还有你
And you.
我们把这些隔板堆在一起
Let's stack these as barricades.
堵住大门
Block the gate.
不可能
Outta here.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
谁输的筹码都没了
Who's got no chips left?
你还好吧
You okay?
我只是 在想事情
I was just...thinking about things.
你如果执意要知道的话 我在
If you really want to know, I was, um...
我在想我父亲
...thinking about my father.
他是个怎样的人
What about him?
嗯 他是个
Well, he was a...
我觉得他是那个阶级背景下的
Well, I suppose he was rather typical for an Englishman
典型英国人
of his class and background.
聪明至极 成功至极 还非常有原则
Highly intelligent, highly principled, very successful.
他为我定的标准极高 高到可笑
He set this absurdly high bar for me to achieve,
在我达不到时
and then whenever I failed,
他会用尽办法骂我 罚我
he found ways to scold and punish me.
我总是拼命想求他认可
I was always desperate to impress him.
这也是我来这里打拼的原因
That's why I came to live here.
我想创造属于我自己的东西
I wanted to create something of my own
能让我父亲为我骄傲的东西
that would make my father at least proud of me.
我觉得你已经做到了
I think that's exactly what you've done.
是吗
Is it?
可在我看来 我搞砸了一切
Seems to me that I'm making rather a mess of things.
汤斯顿先生 你敢于跟一群混蛋对峙
Mr. Tunstall, you're up against some real mean motherfuckers.
我为你的勇气骄傲
I'm proud of you for standing up to'em.
看看周围吧
Just look around.
你身后站着这片土地上最优秀的人
You got some of the best souls in the territory behind you.
他们诚实 善良
Good, honest people.
仅凭这一点 你就成功了
That alone tells me you're succeeding.
您父亲只要不疯不傻
And if your father had any sense or understanding,
他就会明白的
he'd see that himself.
谢谢你 比利
Thank you, Billy.
我这话你可能不爱听
You are not going to want to hear this.
但我不能拿这些人的生命冒险
But I can't put the lives of all these people on the line.
我不想眼看
I don't want to see
这么多正义之士因我被杀
all these honest and decent folk getting killed in my name.
我不想决一死战 至少现在不想
I don't want a showdown. Not yet, anyway.
可你说过我们得面对他们
You said we had to stand up to'em.
你说过我们别无选择
You said we didn't have a choice.
也许我们有的选
Well, maybe we do have a choice.
我刚在想 也许我们可以在警长来之前
I was just thinking that we could move
把马匹转移到别处
the horses before the sheriff gets here.
我在堡垒附近另买了一个农场
I bought another farm up near the fort
我们可以把人马带到那里 从长计议
and we can take them there and then figure out
我觉得警长不会来追
the next step and I don't think the sheriff will follow us.
不 我们不能总是逃避
No, we can't keep runnin'away.
你觉得我是脓包 是吗
You think I'm being a coward, don't you?
我不想让你和这些人为我送命
I don't want you or any of these people to die for me.
我会无法面对自己
I couldn't live with myself.
我情愿你们觉得我是脓包
Now if that makes me a coward, so be it.
快点吧
－ Come on.
我们得赶在武装队之前离开
We gotta clear out before the posse gets here.
汤斯顿先生觉得警长不会来追
Mr. Tunstall thinks the sheriff won't try and follow us.
但我不敢肯定
But I ain't so sure.
你们俩轮流垫后 保持警惕
You two take it in turns to drop back and check.
所以 你父亲呢
So, what about your father?
他是个什么样的人
What kind of a man was he?
他是个骄傲的爱尔兰人
He was a proud Irishman.
他从未想过背井离乡
He never wanted to leave.
尽管那里已经没什么值得他留恋的了
There just wasn't much left for him there.
事实证明 纽约也不适合移民居住
Turns out there wasn't much for immigrants in New York either.
-所以你是穷人咯  -非常穷
So, you were poor? - Oh, dirt poor.
所以我父母才决定西行
That's why my parents decided to come out west.
想过上更好的生活
To find a better life.
是
Yeah...
一定很难吧
It must have been hard.
马车行进的路上 我父亲生病了
Somewhere along the wagon trail, my father got sick.
他失去了求生意志
He kinda gave up.
你爱你父亲吗 比利
Did you love him, Billy? Your father?
他虽然是我父亲
He was my father.
但却放弃了我
But he quit on me.
我发誓 比利
I swear to you, Billy,
我不会让你失望的
I won't let you down.
他们不在这 杰西
They're not here, Jesse.
行了 我又不瞎
AII right! You think I can't see that?
追上他们 小伙子们
Let's follow'em, boys!
我觉得我们不该那么做
I don't think we should do that.
为啥
Why not?
我们只是布雷迪的武装队
We're just Brady's posse.
从法律上讲 我们要做的就是
Legally, all we're supposed to do
给汤斯顿送达传票 抓几匹马走
is serve Tunstall a writ, seize some horses.
而不是追着他走过半个国家
Not chase him halfway across the country.
我们就他妈是法律
We are the fuckin' law!
-我们想干什么就干什么  -杰西说的对
- We do what we want, boys. - Jesse's right.
就是这么跟我们说的 我们也就该这么做
That's what we've been told. That's what we outta do.
这是个坏主意
It's a bad idea.
我们得跟警长说声
We gotta talk to the sheriff.
你们是有什么毛病
What is wrong with all of ya?
我们都知道来这到底该做什么
We all know what we are really meant to do here.
我跟你们说 我的刀已磨光
I tell you, my knife is sharp
就等着杀人剥皮了
and I feel like scalping someone!
所以赶紧跟我去追他们吧 小伙子们
So, let's get after em, boys! Come on!
驾 驾
Hiya! Hiya! Hiya!
杰西 这些痕迹看上去是新的
Jesse, these tracks look fresh.
有人跟踪吗 乔治
Anyone following, George?
没有 一个人影都看不到
No. AII clear. Didn't see a soul.
好吧
AII right.
你们饿了吗
You boys hungry?
饿了 看到午餐了 走吧
Yes, and there's our lunch. Come on.
去吧
Let's go!
去吧比利 你可是神枪手
Go on, Billy. You're the best marksman.
去给咱们抓午餐吧
Go get us some lunch.
走了 汤姆
Come on, Tom.
小心点马 汤斯顿先生
Mind the horses, Mr. Tunstall.
觉得今天有的吃吗
Think we gonna eat today? -
如果他们真能打中什么的话
Maybe if they can actually hit anything.
靠
Ah, shitl
是杰西和他手下
It's Jesse and his boys.
他要去哪
Where's he goin'?
驾
Hiya! Ya!
早了 汤斯顿先生落单了
Ah shit. That's Tunstall. He's on his own.
我这就去救他 在这等我
I'm gonna go get him. Wait here.
我真不该留下他一人的
- - I shouldn't have left him.
不该丢下他一人
I shouldn't have left him.
不
No!
草
Fuck! -
如何
Well?
黎明时分 他们带着马从汤斯顿的牧场出发
They struck out from Tunstall's ranch around dawn, with horses.
我们寻迹跟上了他们 抓了个正着
Picked up their trail, and we caught up with them.
然后呢
And then?
然后发生了火拼
And there was a firefight.
我们有合法权力来扣押这些马匹
Now we had legal authority to seize those animals,
但他们却进行了抵抗
but they were bent on resisting.
我们担心自己的生命安全
We were afraid for our lives.
终于 我们见到了汤斯顿本人
Finally, we tracked down Tunstall himself.
我们让他投降 但他拒绝了
We told him to surrender, but he just refused.
他朝我们开枪 我们反击
He fired at us, and we fired back.
你说他死了
And you're saying he's dead?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
拒捕吗
Resisting arrest?
是的 警长
Yes, Sheriff.
你他妈觉得这事哪里好笑
In what fucking universe do you find this amusing?
你做的事会给我们所有人
What you've done may have terrible consequences
都招来恶果
for all of us.
所以别他妈跟我笑嘻嘻的
So don't look so fucking happy.
你给了我希望
You gave me hope.
一个新生活
A new life.
我以我已逝的母亲起誓
I swear on my mother's grave...
我会杀掉所有害死你的人
...I will kill every man involved in your murder,
付出生命也在所不惜 所以上帝请你帮我
or die myself in the attempt, so help me God.
我们终于弄死了那个混蛋
We finally got the fucker!
圣诞他妈的快乐 所有人
Happy fucking Christmas, everybody!
先生们
Gentlemen! Ho- ho!
听我说一句 小伙子们 注意了
Listen up, boys. Listen up.
今天是浩世的大日子
Today is a great day for the House.
所以我建议敬创始人
And that is why I want to salute the founder
战争英雄墨菲上校一杯
Major Murphy, a war hero.
敬墨菲上校
To Major Murphy.
墨菲上校 墨菲上校
Major Murphy! Major Murphy!
来点音乐啊
Where's the music?
你好啊
Howdy.
你来这有什么事吗
What's your business here today?
我要跟浩世的莱利先生开会
I have a meeting with Mr. Riley at the House,
不知道这事跟你有啥关系
if it's any of your business.
-你叫什么  -埃德加·沃尔兹
- What's your name? - My name's Edgar Walz.
我是托马斯·卡特伦的代表律师
I represent Thomas Catron.
我听说过他
I heard of him.
那你又是谁呢
Who might you be?
杰西·埃文斯
I'm Jesse Evans.
久闻大名啊
I've heard of you.
他们告诉我说你是个危险人物
They, um, they tell me you're a dangerous man.
我喜欢
I like that.
嗯 那要看你怎么理解危险了 沃尔兹先生
Yeah, well, depends on what you mean by dangerous, Mr. Walz.
我的意思是 我今后可能用得着你
What I mean is I might have a use for you.
也许在未来的某个时候
In due course.
很高兴认识你 埃文斯先生
I'm glad we met, Mr. Evans.
叫我杰西就行
Call me Jesse.
你可真友善
That's very kind of you.
现在 杰西
Now Jesse...
我能过了吗
May I pass?
没问题
Sure.
王八蛋
Prick.
所以
So...
我是来通知你 卡特伦先生
I came to inform you that Mr. Catron is very pleased
对约翰·汤斯顿不再参与林肯县经济事务一事
with the termination of John Tunstall's interest
深感高兴
in the economic affairs of Lincoln County.
谢谢
Thank you.
没人想看到这样的结果
It's something that no one wanted,
但汤斯顿先生毕竟犯了法
but the fact remains that Tunstall was a criminal.
真是让人难过啊
It's all been very sad.
但是我还是要提醒你
However, I must remind you
你还欠卡特伦先生一大笔债
that you are still in substantial debt to Mr. Catron.
而且卡特伦先生对目前的情况还是不满意
And Mr. Catron remains unhappy with the current situation.
我不明白
Well, I don't understand.
汤斯顿不挡路了 情况就完全改变了啊
With Tunstall outta the way, things have completely changed.
你是觉得我傻吗 莱利先生
Do you take me for a fool, Mr. Riley?
马上就要开战了
There's a serious war going on,
卡特伦先生非常担心
and Mr. Catron is very concerned
这个比利小子
that this, um, Billy the Kid can,
靠他一人就能给你的生意和手下
on his own account, inflict serious damage
造成重创
on your business and employees.
我们可以处理
We can handle it.
我们有枪
We've got the guns
而且浩世也是个大机构
and the House is a fuckin' institution.
而且我觉得是时候
And I think it's about time
你表现出一点尊敬了 沃尔兹先生
that you start respecting that, Mr. Walz.
想知道我怎么看的吗 莱利
Wanna know how I see it, Riley?
浩世即将面临严重的财务危机
The House is facing imminent financial disaster.
鉴于情况危急
So, in view of this perilous situation,
卡特伦先生建议你将
Mr. Catron is suggesting that you mortgage to him
林肯县的所有股份抵押给他
all your holdings in Lincoln County.
作为回报卡特伦先生会借给你25000美元
In return, Mr. Catron will lend you 25, 000 dollars,
三个月内偿还即可
repayable in three months'time.
如果你拖欠贷款
If you default on the loan, however,
卡特伦先生将拥有所有抵押财产
Mr. Catron will own all mortgaged property.
我以为我们是在合伙做生意
I thought that we were in business together.
莱利先生 你不会不知道吧 在所有商业交易中
Mr. Riley, don't you know that in all business transactions
都有一个主导的合伙人
there is one leading partner.
我他妈上哪去弄这笔钱
How the fuck am I supposed to find this money?
那是你的事了
That's your business.
但我建议你尽快
But I suggest you bring an end to this war
结束这场战斗
as promptly as possible.
来吧 莱利先生
Come, come, Mr. Riley.
我之前就说过 在商言商
I've told you before, this is business.
生意里可容不下你的多愁善感
There's no sentiment in business.
现在 如果你接受这个抵押协议
Now, if you accept the terms of this mortgage agreement,
请在这份具有法律效力的文件上签字吧
please sign this legal and binding document.
非常好
Wonderful.
很荣幸跟您合作
Been a pleasure.
就不用送了
I'll see myself out.
这结果你没想到吗
What'd you expect?
我很久以前就跟你说过
I told you a long time ago,
跟卡特伦这种人合作就是你太天真了
you are too naive be dealing with a man like Catron.
他可比你精明多了
He's smarter than you'll ever be.
我不用愚蠢酒鬼给我什么狗屁建议
I don't need any fuckin'advice from a stupid old drunk!
你不会开枪的
You won't shoot me.
你一开枪就什么都没有了 莱利
The minute you shoot me, Riley, you lose everything!
好好想想吧
Think about that.
我是唯一能跟卡特伦说上话的人
I'm the only person that can talk to Catron.
他也只会听我的
And I'm the only person he'll listen to.
来吧 开枪啊
Go on, shoot me.
你他妈开枪啊
Fuckin'shoot me!
哦 愿你把我藏在阴间
O that thou wouldest hide me in the grave,
愿你把我隐瞒
that thou wouldest keep me secret,
等你的忿怒过去
until thy wrath be past,
愿你为我定一个日期 记念我
that thou wouldest appoint me a set time, and remember me.
人死了岂能再活呢
If a man die, shall he live again?
我只要在我一切争战的日子等候
AlI the days of my appointed time will I wait,
等我被改变
- till my change come. -
你呼唤 我就回答你
Thou shalt call, and I will answer thee.
你必切望自己手所做的工
Thou wilt have a desire to the work
恶人的计算
of thine hands. For now thou numberest my steps.
你也必顾念
Dost thou not watch over my sin?
我的过犯被封在囊中
My transgression is sealed up in a bag,
你缝补了我的罪孽
and thou sewest up mine iniquity.
山崩必归于无有
And surely the mountains falling cometh to nought,
磐石必因所挪开而不在原处
and the rock is removed...
先生们 请安静
Gentlemen, please, let's have some order!
谢谢大家
Thank you.
我必须指出 我们的首要任务
I have to tell you that our first duty
是要找出一个合法方案
is to try and find a legal solution,
而不是自行执法
rather than take the law into our own hands.
所以明天 我会起诉布雷迪警长
So tomorrow, I will charge all the members
武装队的所有人 还有莱利
of Sheriff's Brady's posse, as well as Riley
以及浩世集团的墨菲
and Murphy of the House,
涉嫌共谋杀害约翰·汤斯顿
with complicity in the murder of John Tunstall.
我还会要求将汤斯顿的产业
I will also demand the return of Tunstall's store
归回于我和布鲁尔先生
to myself and Mr. Brewer.
麦克斯文先生
Mr. McSween!
我理解你对程序正义的尊重
I understand your faith in the due process of the law,
但我不能共席
but I do not share it.
这在林肯县不存在 在新墨西哥不存在
Not here in Lincoln. Not in New Mexico.
大家都很清楚 布雷迪警长
It is clear to all of us that Sheriff Brady,
圣达菲的法院
along with the courts of Santa Fe
包括其他议员都是一丘之貉
and all the other lawmakers are corrupt,
他们不配我们信任
and no longer deserve our trust.
比利 我祈求你 我们需要法律的支持
Billy, I beg you. We need the law on our side.
法律 麦克斯文 这里没有法律
What law, McSween? There is no law.
只有我们
It is just us.
我们决定订立誓约
And what we're decided upon is a pledge
组建一支部队 跟浩世开战
to form a fighting force, to take this war to the House.
我们应该自称监管者
And we should call ourselves the Regulators.
我们苦枉法之徒久矣
That's those who assemble to regulate
所以团结在一起进行监管和纠正
or set to right an intolerable or illegal situation.
我们提名比利为领袖
We nominate Billy to be our leader.
同意
Here. Here.
是时候了
Now's the time.
好吧
Okay.
我会带领大家 我们会拼尽全力
I'|I lead you and we'll fight like hell.
但我不想做的事 绝不会逼大家上前
But I will not ask you to do anything I wouldn't do myself.
大家同进同退 这是唯一的办法了
We're in this together. It's the only way.
我明白大家的决定
I understand what's been decided.
我理解个中原因
And, and I can understand why.
但我希望大家明白 用暴力
But I want you all to appreciate that if you respond
对抗暴力
to this act of violence in kind,
将会走上一条不归路
there will be no turning back,
会让这里哀鸿遍野
and there will be a lot of bloodshed.
那就哀鸿遍野吧
Then let there be bloodshed.
谢谢
Gracias.
比利
Billy.
我刚听说汤斯顿先生的事
I just heard about Senor Tunstall.
我很抱歉 我知道他对你很重要
I'm so sorry. I know what he meant to you.
进来吧
Come inside.
比利 这是我哥哥 伊吉尼奥
Billy, this is my brother, Yginio.
-你好  -你好
- Hola. - How do you do?
挺好的 谢谢
Fine, thank you.
你怎么了
What is it?
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
怎么了
What?
我所向往的生活 祈求的未来
The life I'd hoped for, the future I pray for,
都不复存在了
it's all gone.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
我
I.
我得手刃汤斯顿的仇人
I have to kill the men who murdered Tunstall.
你没必要这么做
You don't have to!
警察会逮捕他们 把他们进监绞死的
They will be arrested. Put in jail. Hanged.
在这里不会
Not here.
这里没有法律可言
There's no Iaw here.
我想要正义 就得把王法掌握在自己手中
If I want justice, I have to take the law into my own hands.
这么说你又要当逃犯了
So, you'd be an outlaw again?
一个通缉犯
A wanted man.
你活着一天 就一天不得安宁
Even if you live, you won't have any peace,
过着逃亡的日子 这就是你想要的吗
they'll hunt you down. Is that what you want?
不是我想要的 但我别无选择
No, it's not what I want. But I don't have a choice.
听着 我无法祈求你的同意
Look, I know I can't get your blessing on this,
但我需要你理解
but I need your understanding.
我不理解 你告诉我你变了
Well, I can't understand. You told me you'd changed.
我之前想和你在一起 但现在一切都没了
I wanted to be with you, and now, it's all gone.
不 等等
No wait.
拜托
Please!
不 不
No. No.
你走吧 现在走
Please go. Now!
我下次再看到你的脸
The next time I'll see your face
会是在通缉令上
will be on a"wanted"poster.
嗨 约翰
Hey, John.
-是谁  -我是汤姆·欧费亚德
- Who's that? - My name's Tom O'Folliard.
我有消息你一定想听
I've got some news you might wanna hear
-跟比利小子有关  -什么消息
- about Billy the Kid. - What kind of news?
你拿枪对着我 我当然不会说
I'm not gonna tell you if you're gonna shoot me.
好吧 我不开枪
Well, I ain't gonna shoot ya.
你要说什么
Tell me what you got.
别他妈出声 不然你就死定了
Don't make a fuckin' noise or you're dead.
给我站起来
Now get the fuck up.
嘘 别出声
Shh. Shush now.
我不想伤害你 贝克维斯
Now, I don't want to hurt you, Beckwith.
不 让我换个说法
No, let me put that another way.
我可以伤害你 但要是你
I wouldn't mind, but I won't
乖乖交代 我就放你一马
as long as you give us the information we need.
我一个字都不会说的
I ain't telling you shit!
我只想知道杀害汤斯顿
Now, I just want to know the names
凶手的名字
of those who killed Tunstall.
我不知道 我当时不在
I don't know. I wasn't there.
你当然知道 贝克维斯
Sure you know, Beckwith.
我给你五秒钟 就这样
I'|| give you five seconds and that's it.
5 4 3
- - 5, 4, 3,
2 1
2, 1...
我拿到名字了
Got the names.
杀害汤斯顿的人
The ones who killed Tunstall.
是贝克 莫顿和奥林杰
It was Baker, Morton and Olinger.
没有杰西
Not Jesse?
我不知道
I don't know.
贝克维斯说没有
Beckwith says not.
我们先等等 看看麦克斯文从法庭带来的消息
First, we see if McSween has made any progress in the courts.
然后呢
And then?
然后再说
And then...we'll see.
比利
Billy.
怎么了 麦克斯文
What is it, McSween?
威尔逊法官只能保证 把汤斯顿的店铺
AlI Judge Wilson was able to secure was the return
交还原来的主人
of Tunstall's store to its original owners.
至于刑事指控
As far as the criminal charges are concerned,
由于阿克塞特尔州长的干预 他无能为力
no less a person than State Governor Axtell has intervened.
真是扯淡
Oh, this is bullshit.
对不起 比利
I'm sorry, Billy.
法律让我们失望了
The law has let us down.
腐败是这里的家常便饭 亚历山大
The corruption shouldn't come as a surprise to you, Alexander.
他们现在也会盯上你的
And they'll be gunning for you now as well.
我建议你俩马上离开林肯
I suggest the two of you leave Lincoln.
-可是   -不 亲爱的 不
- But...No, dear. No.
我们现在得听比利的
We have to listen to Billy now.
这一切都始于他们盗走了
You know all of this started with them stealing
汤斯顿先生的马
Tunstall's horses.
我们要回敬他们一局
So I say we send them a fuckin' message
拿回属于我们的东西
and take back what's ours.
我知道杰西的人把马藏在哪儿了
I know where Jesse's gang is holding them.
他们在莫顿那里
They're with Morton.
莫顿
Morton?
那就让监管者骑马过去
So the Regulators ride over there.
收回我们的合法财产
And we reclaim our Iegal property.
我们的马就在那儿
Those are our horses.
那是贝克和他的马
That's Baker with his horse.
跟他在一起的肯定是莫顿
Pretty sure that's Morton with him.
比利的人来了
That's Billy's gang!
胡安 你负责把马圈走 咱们上
Juan, you secure the horses. Let's go.
莫顿
Morton!
驾 驾
Hiya, hiya!
来吧
Hiya! Come on!
莫顿 马中枪了
Morton! The horse is done.
快骑 快骑
Ride, ride, ride, ride!
查理 米德尔顿 从左边包抄他们
Charlie, Middleton, flank them on the left.
注意隐蔽
Cover.
啊 我中枪了 我中枪了
Ah! I'm hit, I'm hit.
别开枪
Hold your fire.
比利
Billy!
莫顿和贝克
Morton and Baker!
你们没机会的
You got no chance!
放下武器 举起手出来
Throw your weapons down and come out with your hands up.
现在投降 我保证你安全回到林肯
Surrender now and I promise you safe passage back to Lincoln.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
比利不会让我们走的
Billy's not gonna let us walk away.
我向你保证
You have my word.
把枪扔了 束手就擒
Now throw out your guns and come on out!
好了 我们要出来了 别开枪
AII right, we're coming out now. Don't shoot.
该死
Goddamit.
林肯的王法现在归我们了
We're the law in Lincoln now.